sukh-dukh.com 2013-04-14

# SukhDukh.com Privacy Policy

Sukhdukh.com gives utmost importance to your privacy. We respect and are committed to protecting your privacy. We follow standard industry practices to maintain your personal information. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. 

**1\. Policy Coverage**  
This Privacy Policy covers Sukhdukh.com's treatment of personally identifiable information that Sukhdukh.com collects when you are on the Sukhdukh.com site, and when you use Sukhdukh.com's services. This policy also covers Sukhdukh.com's treatment of any personally identifiable information that Sukhdukh.com's business partner's share with Sukhdukh.com. 

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Sukhdukh.com does not own or control, or to people that Sukhdukh.com does not employ or manage. 

**2\. Information collected by Sukhdukh.com**  
Sukhdukh.com collects personally identifiable information. Personally identifiable information includes information such as your name, address, email address, birth date, gender, occupation, industry, personal interests etc. Once you have sent us this information and sign in to our services, you are given a unique 'Sukhdukh ID' and are not anonymous to us anymore. 

**3\. Use of information by Sukhdukh.com**  
Sukhdukh.com will not with share your personally identifiable information with third parties. Sukhdukh.com may use the information to inform you regarding any new facilities that may be offered on the site from time to time.   
We understand that our number one asset is our 'members' and we will never knowingly do anything to harm the trust you have bestowed on us. We use any information voluntarily you give us to enhance your experience in our site, which is to provide you with interactive or personalized elements on the sites and to better prepare future content based on your interests. We aggregate this tracking information to determine which areas of our site members like and don't like, based on traffic to those areas. This helps us continue to build a better service for you. 

Sukhdukh.com is a free website and our revenues are derived from advertising. When you become a member of Sukhdukh.com we ask you a series of general demographic questions. We use the information that is gathered to tailor our content to suit your needs and help our advertisers better understand our audience's demographics. This is essential to keep our service free.
